A Guide to the Records of the Policy Office of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2001
Library of Virginia
- Series V. Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1998-2001., Extent: 27 folders. (Box 4-5)
  - Virginia's Family Access to Medical Insurance Security Plan (FAMIS) (CMSIP) - Briefing Book on Children's Health Insurance developed by the Department of Medical Assistance Services, Fall 1999 (part one) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Virginia's Family Access to Medical Insurance Security Plan (FAMIS) (CMSIP) - Briefing Book on Children's Health Insurance developed by the Department of Medical Assistance Services, Fall 1999 (part two) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Virginia's Family Access to Medical Insurance Security Plan (FAMIS) (CMSIP) - Briefing Book on Children's Health Insurance developed by the Department of Medical Assistance Services, Fall 1999 (part three) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Family Access to Medical Insurance Security Plan (FAMIS) - Information Packet (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Right Choices for Youth Conference, Leader's Notebook - 1999 September 23 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Right Choices for Youth - Information Packet, Videotapes (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Right Choices for Youth - Information Packet (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Right Choices for Youth - Information Packet (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Right Choices for Youth - Information Packet (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation & Substance Abuse Services - Copy of Gellar Report along with Governor Gilmore's Talking Points, 1998 July (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation & Substance Abuse Services - Development of Comprehensive Community and Facilities Master Plan for Delivery of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services in Virginia, Combined Technical and Cost Proposal, submitted by J & E Associations and BTG Research Division, 1998 March 23 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation & Substance Abuse Services - Development of Comprehensive Community and Facilities Master Plan for Delivery of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services in Virginia, Supplemental Reports, submitted by J & E Associations and BTG Research Division, 1998 September (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Department of Mental Health, Mental Retardation & Substance Abuse Services - Mental Health Reform Plan, Press Release and Newspaper Articles, 2000 December - 2001 January (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Developmental Disabilities Waiver, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Mental Retardation Waiver, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Electronic Benefits Transfer (EBT) Project - Status Report, 2001 November 30 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Food Stamp Error Rate, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Child Placing Regulations - Talking Points (Draft), 2000 June ("Spanking Regulations") (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Hugh Finn Case - Hearing Transcript, Circuit Court of Prince William County, Chancery No. 39711, 1998 July 29 (part one) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Hugh Finn Case - Hearing Transcript, Circuit Court of Prince William County, Chancery No. 39711, 1998 July 29 (part two) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Hugh Finn Case - Hearing Transcript, Circuit Court of Prince William County, Chancery No. 39711, 1998 July 29 (part three) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Hugh Finn Case - Motion for Expedited Hearing, Michelle Finn, Guardian versus Commonwealth of Virginia (Claude Allen, Secretary of Health and Human Resources; Dennis Smith, Director, Department of Medical Assistance Services; William Nelson, Acting State Health Commissioner, Virginia Department of Health; and Mark Early, Attorney General), Circuit Court of Prince William County, Chancery No 39711, 1998 September 23 (includes Hugh Finn admission fact sheet [RESTRICTED] and affidavit of Marie F. Saul) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Hugh Finn Case - Court documents pertaining to the case, James S. Gilmore, III, Governor of the Commonwealth of Virginia and the Commonwealth of Virginia v. Annaburg Manor Nursing Home, Robin B. Merlino, M.D. and Michelle Finn, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Hugh Finn Case - Correspondence and Newspaper Clippings, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous - Memo to John A. Mahone, Governor Gilmore's Deputy Chief of Staff from Louis F. Rossiter, Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2001 August 15 - outlining documents Governor may wish to retain (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Series VI. Secretary of Natural Resources, 1998-2001., Extent: 23 folders. (Box 5-6)
  The Secretary of Natural Resources series is housed in 23 folders and is arranged alphabetically by state agency. Agencies include: Department of Conservation and Recreation, Department of Environmental Quality and Department of Game and Inland Fisheries. Notable files include: Governor Gilmore's briefing book for the 8 December 1998 meeting of the Executive Council of the Chesapeake Bay Program; and a Wetlands Issues briefing book (22 November 1999).
  - Department of Conservation and Recreation - 1999-2000 Biennial Report of the Virginia Land Conservation Foundation (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Department of Conservation and Recreation - The Biennial Nonpoint Source Pollution Water Quality Assessment Report (2000) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Department of Environmental Quality - Recommendations for 8-hour Ozone Nonattainment Areas, 2000 June (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Department of Environmental Quality - Total Maximum Daily Load Program - A Ten Year Implementation Plan (2000 November 1) (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Department of Environmental Quality - Comprehensive Evaluation of Solid Waste Management in the Commonwealth, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Department of Environmental Quality - Virginia Environmental Education Advisory Committee (VEEAC) Report, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Department of Environmental Quality - Chesapeake Bay Commission 2000 Annual Report, "Keeping the Agreement" (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Department of Environmental Quality - 2000 Annual Report on Status of Tributary Strategies, Chesapeake Bay Agreement and Water Quality for Virginia's Chesapeake Bay and Tributaries, 2000 November (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Department of Environmental Quality - Annual Report on the Virginia Water Quality Improvement Fund, Point Source Pollution Control, 2001 January (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Department of Environmental Quality - Citizens Wetlands Advisory Committee Report, 1999 September 30 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Department of Environmental Quality - Virginia Outdoors Plan, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Department of Game and Inland Fisheries - Interim Report of the Virginia Wetlands Restoration Coordinating Committee, 2001 July (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Report on the Management of Municipal Solid Waste in the Commonwealth of Virginia-A Historical Review, 1999 November (copy one) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Report on the Management of Municipal Solid Waste in the Commonwealth of Virginia-A Historical Review, 1999 November (copy two) (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Executive Council of the Chesapeake Bay Program - Governor Gilmore's Briefing Book for 1998 December 8 Meeting (part one) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Executive Council of the Chesapeake Bay Program - Governor Gilmore's Briefing Book for 1998 December 8 Meeting (part two) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Executive Council of the Chesapeake Bay Program - Governor Gilmore's Briefing Book for 1998 December 8 Meeting (part three) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Wetlands Issues, Prepared for Governor James S. Gilmore, III by John Paul Woodley, Jr., Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 November 22 (part one) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Wetlands Issues, Prepared for Governor James S. Gilmore, III by John Paul Woodley, Jr., Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999 November 22 (part two - folder found within briefing binder) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Draft of Master Plan for Jamestown, 1999 October 6 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Natural Resources Briefing for Governor Gilmore, 2000 May 2 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Report of the Shark Attack Task Force, 2002 January 9 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous - E-mail to John A. Mahone, Governor Gilmore's Deputy Chief of Staff from Elwyn Darden, Assistant Secretary of Natural Resources, 2001 September 19 - outlining documents Governor may wish to retain (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Series VII. Secretary of Public Safety, 1998-2001., Extent: 5 boxes. (Box 6-11)
  The Secretary of Public Safety series is housed in 5 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by state agency followed by miscellaneous materials. Agencies include: Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control, Department of Corrections, Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council, Department of Correctional Education, Department of Criminal Justice Services, Department of Emergency Services, Department of Fire Programs, Department of Juvenile Justice, Department of Military Affairs, Virginia Parole Board, and Virginia State Police.
  Notable files under the Dept. of Corrections include: contracts for housing prisoners from Delaware, Michigan and the District of Columbia, 1998; Decision Briefs, 1999-2001; Executions, 1998-2000; and records chronicling the Department of Corrections dispute/litigation with Virginia Correctional Enterprises, 1998-2000.
  Notable files under the Dept. of Emergency Services include: Decision Briefs, 1998-2001; Drought, 1999; Hurricane Floyd, 1999-2000; and Terrorism, 1998-2001.
  Notable files under the Virginia State Police include: Decision Briefs, 1998-2000; and Virginia Exile, 1998-1999.
  Notable files under Miscellaneous include: overview of Project Exile, 1998; "Public Safety Response to Terrorism: Governor's Terrorism Consequence Management Briefing", ca. 1998; and meeting materials from the Congressional Advisory Panel to Assess Preparedness for Weapons of Mass Destruction (13 December 1999 meeting in Santa Monica, California and 28-29 September 2000 meeting in Richmond, Virginia).
  - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control - Litigation: Bolick, et. al. v. Virginia Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control, et. al. and Joyce A. Sutton v. Commonwealth of Virginia and Virginia Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control, Correspondence, 1999 (copy one) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control - Litigation: Bolick, et. al. v. Virginia Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control, et. al. and Joyce A. Sutton v. Commonwealth of Virginia and Virginia Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control, Correspondence, 1999 (copy two) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control - Privatization Study, 1995 January 11 (copy one) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control - Privatization Study, 1995 January 11 (copy two) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control - Studies, 1999 (copy one) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control - Studies, 1999 (copy two) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control - Synar Amendment, 2000 (copy one) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control - Synar Amendment, 2000 (copy two) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control - Tax Program, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control - Tobacco Regulations, 1998-1999 (part one - copy one) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control - Tobacco Regulations, 1998-1999 (part two - copy one) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control - Tobacco Regulations, 1998-1999 (part one - copy two) (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control - Tobacco Regulations, 1998-1999 (part two - copy two) (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control - Underage Drinking Program, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Department of Corrections - Ariens Company (Firelite Camp Stoves), 1998 (copy one) (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Department of Corrections - Ariens Company (Firelite Camp Stoves), 1998 (copy two) (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Department of Corrections - Atmore Drive Lease Briefing, 1998-2000 (copy one) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Department of Corrections - Atmore Drive Lease Briefing, 1998-2000 (copy two) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Department of Corrections - Charlotte County/Drakes Branch Corrections Center, 1997-1998 (copy one) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Department of Corrections - Charlotte County/Drakes Branch Corrections Center, 1997-1998 (copy two) (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Department of Corrections - Compact for Supervision of Adult Probationers and Parolees, Draft Copy, 1999 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Department of Corrections - Contract Beds, Correspondence and Reports, 1998-2001 (copy one) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Department of Corrections - Contract Beds, Correspondence and Reports, 1998-2001 (copy two) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Department of Corrections - District of Columbia Department of Corrections Contract, 1998 (copy one) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Department of Corrections - District of Columbia Department of Corrections Contract, 1998 (copy two) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Department of Corrections - Delaware Contract, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Department of Corrections - Michigan Contract, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Department of Corrections - Senate Finance Committee Presentation on Out of State Contracts, 1998 July 17 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Department of Corrections - Contract Prisons, Correspondence, 1997-1998 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Department of Corrections - Decision Briefs, 1999-2001 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Department of Corrections - Drug Testing, Report of Interagency Drug Offender Screening and Assessment Committee, 2000 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Department of Corrections - Executions, 1998-2000 (copy one) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Department of Corrections - Executions, 1998-2000 (copy two) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Department of Corrections - Headquarters Building, Correspondence, 1999 (copy one) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Department of Corrections - Headquarters Building, Correspondence, 1999 (copy two) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Department of Corrections - Inmates (Charles Apple,1998) [Restricted] (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Department of Corrections - Inmates (Anthony J. Bosoni,1999) (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Department of Corrections - Inmates (Connie F. Gorley,1998) (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Department of Corrections - Inmates (Clyde Johnson,1996-1997) (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Department of Corrections - Inmates (Robert L. Landrum, 1998) (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Department of Corrections - Inmates (Shannon Motley, 1999) (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Department of Corrections - Inmates (Michael Linwood Paley, 1998-1999) (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Department of Corrections - Inmates (Robert Runion, 1999) (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Department of Corrections - Inmates (Calvin Swann, 1999) [Restricted] (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Department of Corrections - Inmate Population Forecast, 1999-2000 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Department of Corrections - Inmate Health Care, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Department of Corrections - Inmate Medical Costs/Care, 1999-2001 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Department of Corrections - Lorton Contract Meeting, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Department of Corrections - Medical Clemency Considerations, 1998-2001 [Restricted] ( 2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Department of Corrections - Morton Marks v. Virginia Correctional Enterprises, 1998 (part one, copy one) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Department of Corrections - Morton Marks v. Virginia Correctional Enterprises, 1998 (part two, copy one) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Department of Corrections - Morton Marks v. Virginia Correctional Enterprises, 1998 (part one, copy two) (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Department of Corrections - Morton Marks v. Virginia Correctional Enterprises, 1998 (part two, copy two) (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Department of Corrections - Pardon Requests, 1998-2000 [Restricted] (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Department of Corrections - Red Onion Prison, 1998-2001 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Department of Corrections - Sentence Reductions, 1998-2000 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Department of Corrections - Sexually Violent Predators (SVP), 2000 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Department of Corrections - Sussex II Prison, 1998-1999 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Department of Corrections - Teko Williams, 1997-1998 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Department of Corrections - Violent Offender Incarceration and Truth-in-Sentencing (VOI-TIS) Federal Grant Program, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Department of Corrections - Virginia Correctional Enterprises (VCE), Correspondence and Reports, 1998-2000 (copy one) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Department of Corrections - Virginia Correctional Enterprises (VCE), Correspondence and Reports, 1998-2000 (copy two) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Department of Corrections - Wallens Ridge State Prison, 1998-2000 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council - Administrative Coordinator, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Department of Correctional Education - Beaumont Correctional Center, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Department of Correctional Education - Culpeper Juvenile Correctional Center, 1999 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Department of Correctional Education - Juvenile Student Demographic Report, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Department of Correctional Education - Privatization Report, 1998 January (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Department of Correctional Education - Red Onion Prison, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Department of Correctional Education- Wallens Ridge State Prison, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Department of Criminal Justice Services - Crime Rates, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Department of Criminal Justice Services - Forensic Science, 1997-2001 (copy one) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Department of Criminal Justice Services - Forensic Science, 1997-2001 (copy two) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Department of Criminal Justice Services - Forensic Science, Silva Case, 1997 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Department of Criminal Justice Services - Integrated Criminal Justice Information System (ICJIS), 1998-2000 (copy one) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Department of Criminal Justice Services - Integrated Criminal Justice Information System (ICJIS), 1998-2000 (copy two) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Department of Criminal Justice Services - SABRE, 2000 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Department of Criminal Justice Services - School Resource Officers, 1998-2000 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Department of Criminal Justice Services - Virginia Exile, 1999-2000 (copy one) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Department of Criminal Justice Services - Virginia Exile, 1999-2000 (copy two) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Department of Criminal Justice Services - Virginia Victim Rights Strategic Planning Group, 1997-1998 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Adkins v. Commonwealth of Virginia, 1997 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Cheatham Annex, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Chemical Attack, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Decision Briefs, 1998-2001 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Disaster Plan, 1998-2001 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Drought, 1999 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Emergency Management Assistance Compact (EMAC), 1998 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Emergency Operation Center (EOC), 1998 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Department of Emergency Services - HAZMAT, 1997-1998 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Hurricanes and Hurricane Bonnie, 1998-2001 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Hurricane Floyd, 1999-2000 (copy one) (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Hurricane Floyd, 1999-2000 (copy two) (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Department of Emergency Services - State of Emergency Declaration, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Department of Emergency Services - State of Emergency, Southwest Virginia (1998 January) & Central Virginia (2000 January) (copy one) (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Department of Emergency Services - State of Emergency, Southwest Virginia (1998 January) & Central Virginia (2000 January) (copy two) (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Study of Search and Rescue Efforts, 1999 (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Terrorism, 1998-2001 (copy one) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Terrorism, 1998-2001 (copy two) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Department of Emergency Services - Virginia Operations Plan Exercise, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Department of Fire Programs - Fire Disaster Assistance, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice - Beaumont Juvenile Correctional Center, 1996-2001 (copy one) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice - Beaumont Juvenile Correctional Center, 1996-2001 (copy two) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice - Bon Air Correctional Center, 1999-2001 (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice - Handle With Care Plan, 1999 (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice - Incident Reports, 1998 [RESTRICTED] (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice - LEADER Program, 1998-2000 (copy one) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice - LEADER Program, 1998-2000 (copy two) (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice - Litigation (Baker v. Commonwealth of Virginia; Carbajal v. Parr, et al & Ferris v. Parr, et al; Hamilton v. Dept. of Juvenile Justice; Linden v. Commonwealth of Virginia) [RESTRICTED](2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice - Litigation (Luzik v. Commonwealth & Linden v. Commonwealth) (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice - Oak Ridge Juvenile Correctional Center, 1999-2000 (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice - Personnel, 1998-2001 (copy one) (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice - Personnel, 1998-2001 (copy two) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice - Tour of Bon Air, RDC & LEADER Program by North Carolina Commission on Juvenile Crime and Justice, 1998 February 17 (Box 9, Folder 17a)
  - Department of Military Affairs - Affirmative Action, 1999 (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Department of Military Affairs - Adjutant General Position, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Department of Military Affairs - Camp Pendleton, 1997-2000 (copy one) (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Department of Military Affairs - Camp Pendleton, 1997-2000 (copy two) (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Department of Military Affairs - Counterdrug Support Plan, 1998-1999 (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Department of Military Affairs - Critical Issues for New TAG, 1998 (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Department of Military Affairs - Decision Briefs, 1998-1999 (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Department of Military Affairs - Fort Pickett, 1998-1999 (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Department of Military Affairs - National Guard, 1998-2000 (2 copies) (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Department of Military Affairs - SSG Michael R. Purcell, 1998 [RESTRICTED] (copy one) (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Department of Military Affairs - SSG Michael R. Purcell, 1998 [RESTRICTED] (copy two) (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Department of Military Affairs - Rapid Assessment and Initial Detection (RAID), 1999 (2 copies) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Department of Military Affairs - Rhode Island v. Phyllis N. Segal, et. al., 1998 (2 copies) (Box 10, Folder 2)